[
  {
    "question": "The netmask can't be determined using an IP address and the broadcast address",
    "answers": ["True", "False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "A web server can run on ports different than 80",
    "answers": ["True", "False"],
    "correct": "a"
  },
  {
    "question": "The broadcast address cannot be calculated using the IP address and the netmask",
    "answers": ["True", "False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is TTL?",
    "answers": [
      "Time To Leave",
      "Total Time Limit",
      "Time To Live",
      "Time Tracking Limit"
    ],
    "correct": "c"
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following involve NAT?",
    "answers": [
      "Port Forwading",
      "Accessing the web from an interal network. Your PC's network will be translated to your public IP (i.e., home network)",
      "Address Translation"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "11111111.11111111.11111100.00000000 = 255.255.254.0",
    "answers": ["True", "False"],
    "correct": "a"
  },
  {
    "question": "255.255.128.0 = /23",
    "answers": ["True", "False"],
    "correct": "a"
  },
  {
    "question": "TCP, UDP are part of",
    "answers": [
      "Transport Layer",
      "Link Layer",
      "Application Layer",
      "Internet Layer"
    ],
    "correct": "a"
  },
  {
    "question": "TCP Header contains the following entries:",
    "answers": [
      "Source Port, Destination Port, Route ID, Checksum",
      "Source Mac, Destination Mac, Connection object, Checksum, Data hash",
      "Source IP, Destination IP, Pointer to MAC address, Connection unique identifier, Router IP, NAT tables",
      "Source Port, Destination Port, Sequence Number, Acknowledgement Number, Flags, Data Offset, Checksum, Urgent Pointer"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is a private IP address?",
    "answers": ["12.0.0.2", "172.15.14.36", "168.172.19.40", "192.168.24.43"],
    "correct": "bd"
  },
  {
    "question": "TCP Header contains the following entries:",
    "answers": [
      "Source Port, Destination Port, Route ID, Checksum",
      "b. Source Mac, Destination Mac, Connection object, Checksum, Data hash",
      "c. Source IP, Destination IP, Pointer to MAC address, Connection unique identifier, Router IP, NAT tables",
      "d. Source Port, Destination Port, Sequence Number, Acknowledgement Number, Flags, Data Offset, Checksum, Urgent Pointer"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "The network address cannot be calculated using the broadcast address and the netmask",
    "answers": ["True", "False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "bind() cannot be used in UDP clients",
    "answers": ["True", "False"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following is true about the IP address 10.16.3.65/23?",
    "answers": [
      "The last valid host address in the subnet is 10.16.2.254",
      "The broadcast address of the subnet is 10.16.3.254",
      "The lowest host address in the subnet is 10.16.2.1",
      "The subnet address is 10.16.3.0/255.255.254.0"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "Which one/ones of the following addresses have to be identical for all computers located in the same local network(from a physical and logic point of view)",
    "answers": [
      "MAC Address",
      "IP Address",
      "Broadcast Address",
      "Network Address"
    ]
  },
  {
    "question": "What is the difference between a switch and a hub?",
    "answers": [
      "The switch sends a packet specifically to an end point or more, the hub broadcasts the message to all the network",
      "The hub sends a packet specifically to an end point or more, the switch broadcasts the message to all the network",
      "The hub can send packets on large distances, but the switch is generally for home usage",
      "There is no difference"
    ],
    "correct": "a"
  }
]
